tjshome.com 2016-03-16

# Privacy Policy for Tjshome.com

**Privacy Policy for Tjshome.com ("Tjshome")**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at . 

At Tjshome, the privacy of our visitors is extremely important to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Tjshome and how it is used. 

**Use of Collected Information**

Tjshome.com is the sole owner of any information collected on the website, however, Tjshome does not share any collected information to third parties. 

**Email Addresses**

Tjshome does not share with any third parties email addresses collected through the website. We do not currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form. 

**Comments/Message Boards**

Some of Tjshome pages contain comment sections. We may not be able to actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. 

**Legal proceedings**

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but Tjshome may need to disclose information when required by law. 

**Traffic Reports**

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular. 

**Cookies**

Tjshome does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies or web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Commission Junction, Linkshare, Amazon, and the Google Affiliate Network. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements that appear within Tjshome and they may automatically receive your IP Address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

Google Adsense advertisements uses the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx). Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve custom ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy ](http://www.google.com/privacy_cookies.html). 

Tjshome has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Tjshome's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**Links**

Tjshome frequently links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site's privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to websites on Tjshome.com only. 

**Notification of Changes**

When Tjshome makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here. 

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us. 

_Last modified: 16th December, 2011_
